Come
Come a
Come along
Come along down
Come along down with
Come along down with me
You're
You're not
You're not a
You're not alone
You
You will
You will see
Each o
Each other
Each other is
Each other is all
Each other is all they
Each other is all they need
In
In the
In the hour
In the hour of
In the hour of joy
In
In this
In this pa
In this para
In this paradise
If
If we
If we had
If we had ne
If we had never
If we had never done
The
The things
The things we
The things we did
(Come
(Come a
(Come along
(Come along down
(Come along down with
(Come along down with me)
(Come
(Come a
(Come along)
(Come
(Come a-
(Come a- come
(Come a- come a
(You're
(You're not
(You're not a
(You're not alone)
(You
(You will
(You will see)
(Come
(Come a
(Come along)
(Come
(Come a-
(Come a- come
(Come a- come a
We
Each o
Each other
Each other is
Each other is all
Each other is all we
Each other is all we need
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
(In
(In the
(In the hour
(In the hour of
(In the hour of joy)
Ar
Arti
Artifi
Artificial
Artificial fa
Artificial facade
From
From the
From the fraud
From the fraud of
From the fraud of a
From the fraud of a god
All
All due
All due to
All due to the
All due to the path
That
That we
That we tro
That we trod
We
We just
We just wan
We just wanted
We just wanted to
We just wanted to heal
But
But now
But now our
But now our night
But now our nightmares
But now our nightmares are
But now our nightmares are real
And
And now
And now we'll
And now we'll ne
And now we'll never
And now we'll never wake
And now we'll never wake up
For
For we've
For we've torn
For we've torn a
(We
(We want
(We want free
(We want freedom)
(Free
(Freedom)
(Freedom
(Freedom, free
(Freedom, freedom
We
We all
We all fall
We all fall down
We'll
We'll sleep
We'll sleep well
We'll sleep well now
Dream
Dream dreams
Dream dreams knocked
Dream dreams knocked out
New
New blooms
New blooms when
New blooms when play
New blooms when playtime
New blooms when playtime sprouts
Come
Come a
Come along
Come along, go
Come along, go to
Come along, go to sleep
(Come
(Come a
(Come along)
(Come
(Come a-
(Come a- come
(Come a- come a
And
And leave
And leave here
With
Without
Without a
Without a trace
(Come
(Come a
(Come along)
(Come
(Come a-
(Come a- come
(Come a- come a
Though
Though life
Though life in
Though life in the
Though life in the sha
Though life in the shadows
Is
Isn't
Isn't much
It's
It's be
It's better
It's better than
It's better than li
It's better than living
It's better than living in
It's better than living in a
It's better than living in a cage
(Can
(Can you
(Can you see
(Can you see us?)
(Can
(Can you
(Can you hear
(Can you hear us?)
Ar
Arti
Artifi
Artificial
Artificial fa
Artificial facade
From
From the
From the fraud
From the fraud of
From the fraud of a
From the fraud of a god
All
All due
All due to
All due to the
All due to the path
That
That we
That we tro
That we trod
We
We just
We just wan
We just wanted
We just wanted to
We just wanted to heal
But
But now
But now our
But now our night
But now our nightmares
But now our nightmares are
But now our nightmares are real
And
And now
And now we'll
And now we'll ne
And now we'll never
And now we'll never wake
And now we'll never wake up
For
For we've
For we've torn
For we've torn a
(We
(We want
(We want free
(We want freedom)
(Free
(Freedom)
(Freedom
(Freedom, free
(Freedom, freedom)
We
We all
We all fall
We all fall down
We'll
We'll sleep
We'll sleep well
We'll sleep well now
Dream
Dream dreams
Dream dreams knocked
Dream dreams knocked out
New
New blooms
New blooms when
New blooms when play
New blooms when playtime
New blooms when playtime sprouts
Ar
Arti
Artifi
Artificial
Artificial fa
Artificial facade
From
From the
From the fraud
From the fraud of
From the fraud of a
From the fraud of a god
All
All due
All due to
All due to the
All due to the path
That
That we
That we trod
We
We just
We just wan
We just wanted
We just wanted to
We just wanted to heal
But
But now
But now our
But now our night
But now our nightmares
But now our nightmares are
But now our nightmares are real
And
And now
And now we'll
And now we'll ne
And now we'll never
And now we'll never wake
And now we'll never wake up
We've
We've torn
We've torn a
We've torn apart
Ar
Arti
Artifi
Artificial
Artificial fa
Artificial faca
Artificial faca-ah
Artificial faca-ah-ah
Artificial faca-ah-ah-ah
Artificial faca-ah-ah-ah-ah
Ah-
Ah-ah
Ah-ah-ah
(La-
(La-la
(La-la-la
(La-la-la-la
(La-la-la-la-la
(La-la-la-la-la-la)